var questions =[{
	"question" : "Hasil dari 8 + 4 = ",
	"option1" : "7",
	"option2" : "11",
	"option3" : "12",
	"option4" : "14",
	"answer" : "3"
	}, {
	"question" : "Hasil dari 4 + 3 = ",
	"option1" : "7",
	"option2" : "10",
	"option3" : "18",
	"option4" : "6",
	"answer" : "1"
	}, {
	"question" : "Hasil dari 12 : 4 = ",
	"option1" : "3",
	"option2" : "4",
	"option3" : "2",
	"option4" : "6",
	"answer" : "1"	
	}, {
	"question" : "Hasil dari 17 + 3 = ",
	"option1" : "15",
	"option2" : "22",
	"option3" : "20",
	"option4" : "23",
	"answer" : "3"
	}, {
	"question" : "Hasil dari 32 : 4 = ",
	"option1" : "5",
	"option2" : "6",
	"option3" : "7",
	"option4" : "8",
	"answer" : "4"
	}, {
	"question" : "Sudut sebesar 35 derajat termasuk  = ",
	"option1" : "Sudut pelanar",
	"option2" : "Sudut tumpul",
	"option3" : "Sudut lancip",
	"option4" : "Sudut siku-siku",
	"answer" : "3"
	}, {
	"question" : "Hasil dari 2 x 8 = ",
	"option1" : "18",
	"option2" : "15",
	"option3" : "24",
	"option4" : "16",
	"answer" : "4"
	}, {
	"question" : "Hasil dari 32 + 29 = ",
	"option1" : "61",
	"option2" : "51",
	"option3" : "53",
	"option4" : "63",
	"answer" : "1"
	}, {
	"question" : "Hasil dari 73 - 12 = ",
	"option1" : "53",
	"option2" : "44",
	"option3" : "61",
	"option4" : "51",
	"answer" : "3"
	}, {
	"question" : "Hasil dari 5 x 8 = ",
	"option1" : "40",
	"option2" : "35",
	"option3" : "45",
	"option4" : "30",
	"answer" : "1"
	}
];